<quests>
	<quest id="fpress" item="frenchPress">
		<explination>
			<conversation person="jenn">
                <dialog>I really need a new french press.</dialog>
				<node>
					<action topic="frenchPress" />
					<player>Why?</player>
					<dialog>I'm not sure... It's in a place.</dialog>
                    <node id="why">
                        <player>Why don't you just go get one?</player>
                        <dialog>I probably will once I'm finished working.  Why did you ask how you could help me if you're just going to patronize me?</dialog>
                    </node>
                    <node>
                        <player>What do you need it for?</player>
                        <dialog>To make coffee silly! What else do you do with a french press?</dialog>
                    </node>
                    <node>
                        <player>Where would I find a french press?</player>
                        <dialog>The junk yard has a lot of random discarded stuff.  I was going to start looking there later.</dialog>
                        <node>
                            <player>Um... How do I go there?</player>
                            <dialog>*Sigh* Click on the link to the left that says "Enter Maze"</dialog>
                        </node>
                    </node>
                    <node cha="5">
                        <player>What are you doing right now?</player>
                        <dialog>I'm packing coffeebeans.  It is quite exhausting.</dialog>
                        <node>
                            <player>Why are you packing coffee beans?</player>
                            <dialog>It’s for my business.  I sell coffee beans you see, but I run it all by myself.</dialog>
                            <node>
                                <player>Why not get someone else to package the beans?</player>
                                <dialog>My business is just starting out.  I don’t have the money to hire another person.</dialog>
                            </node>
                            <node cha="7">
                                <action quest="fpress"></action>
                                <player>I’ll do it for you while you go get a french press, for free!</player>
                                <dialog>Wow that would be great!  I’ll be right back.</dialog>
                            </node>
                            <node>
                                <player>That's too bad.</player>
                                <dialog>Yes, I know.</dialog>
                            </node>
                        </node>
                        <node>
                            <player>That is a weird thing to do.</player>
                            <dialog>It’s not so weird if you run your own store selling coffee beans.  Do you have something better to do?</dialog>
                            <node>
                                <player>Your mom.</player>
                                <dialog>How mature… Well if you’re finished I’m going to get back to my work.  It wouldn’t bother me if I never spoke to you again.</dialog>
                            </node>
                            <node>
                                <player>Sorry, I didn’t mean to be rude.</player>
                                <dialog>It’s quite alright.  But, if you will excuse me I need to get back to my work.</dialog>
                            </node>
                        </node>
                    </node>
				</node>
				<exit>I have to go.</exit>
			</conversation>
		</explination>
		<information>
			<conversation person="kanye" topic="need">
                <dialog>What do you need to know?</dialog>
				<node>
					<player>Do you know where I can find a french press?</player>
					<dialog>What would you ever do with that?</dialog>
					<node>
						<player>I don't know... Make coffee?</player>
						<dialog>Yeah, well, I've never seen one.</dialog>
						<node>
							<player>Ok, thanks for nothing.</player>
							<dialog>Screw you.</dialog>
						</node>
                        <node>
                            <player>Well, talk to you later then.</player>
                            <dialog>Bye.</dialog>
                        </node>
					</node>
                    <node>
                        <player>Someone I know needs one.</player>
                        <dialog>Try the junkyard.</dialog>
                    </node>
                    <node>
                        <player>Why are you so rude?</player>
                        <dialog>Why are you talking to me?</dialog>
                    </node>
				</node>
				<exit>I've got nothing left to say to you.</exit>
			</conversation>
            <conversation person="vhyatt" topic="frenchPress">
                <dialog>What's that?</dialog>
                <node>
                    <player>Do you perchance have a french press you don't want?</player>
                    <dialog>Um.  I don’t think so.  Do I know you?</dialog>
                    <node>
                        <player>Probably not.  Excuse me I'm {player}.</player>
                        <dialog>Well, it's nice to meet you {player}.  Let me think.  Hmmmmm.  I might have something like that, but I would have no idea where it is.</dialog>
                    </node>
                    <node>
                        <player>If you don't know who I am you probably aren't worth talking to.</player>
                        <dialog>You are mean!</dialog>
                        <node>
                            <player>I’m not mean, I just mean what I say.</player>
                            <dialog>Har har.  I’m laughing so hard right now.  I can’t control myself.  I might pass out… From an overdose of sarcasm!</dialog>
                            <node>
                                <player>Not!</player>
                                <dialog>Hold on a second… The 80s called, they want their jokes back.</dialog>
                                <node>
                                    <player>Oh snap!</player>
                                    <dialog>Ok, now this is so bad it's funny again.  That was Grrrrreat!</dialog>
                                </node>
                            </node>
                        </node>
                        <node>
                            <player>Sorry, not sure what came over me there.</player>
                            <dialog>I forgive you, but maybe you want to check yourself.</dialog>
                            <node>
                                <player>Yeah, I almost wrecked myself</player>
                                <dialog>For shizzy my nizzy.</dialog>
                            </node>
                            <node>
                                <player>You're wack!</player>
                                <dialog>You forgot the wiggiddy wiggiddy...</dialog>
                            </node>
                        </node>
                    </node>
                </node>
                <exit>See ya!</exit>
            </conversation>
		</information>
		<solved>
			<conversation person="jenn">
                <dialog>What is it?</dialog>
				<node>
					<player>How do you like your new french press?</player>
					<dialog>It is wonderful thank you so much!</dialog>
				</node>
                <exit>Great! See you later!</exit>
			</conversation>
		</solved>
	</quest>
	<quest id="britches">
		<explination>
			<conversation person="mdav">
                <dialog>I have a quest most dire my friend.  But beware! This quest is not for the faint of heart, the weak of mind or the faint of spirit.  Do you accept this challenge set before you?</dialog>
				<node id="ask">
                    <player>Excuse me?</player>
                    <dialog>Do you accept this challenge set before you?</dialog>
                    <node>
                        <player>Yes. I accept</player>
                        <dialog>GLORIOUS! Now to business.</dialog>
                        <node id="accepted">
                            <player>Ok, What now?</player>
                            <dialog>Huh? Oh YESSS! Most dire business you see.  Most dire.</dialog>
                            <node>
                                <player>Right, so what do you want me to do.</player>
                                <dialog>Hush my friend.  Don’t speak to loudly.  What we discuss be dire business.</dialog>
                                <node>
                                    <player>Yes.  You mentioned that.</player>
                                    <dialog>I can’t emphasize the sheer gravity of this situation! Ohhh, most dire my child, most dire.</dialog>
                                    <node ref="accepted" />
                                </node>
                                <node id="query">
                                    <player>Is there anything you want me to actually do?</player>
                                    <dialog>Alright, I supposed ‘tis time we get down to brass and tax.  A long time ago, a simpler time if ever there was one, I owned myself the finest pair of britches a man did have in those days, in those times.  However, time has not smiled upon those britches in many a moon.  One could say the sun hath not seen the surface of these britches in their entirety since it did last round the Earth.  As a man of lesser stand, my access to certain amenities has fallen short.  As such these britches, the very ones I wear upon these weary old legs, have not the faintest touch of water, brush or soap in measures larger than might fit in a thimble.  Though it pains me to do so I must beg, if not plead with you to attend to what is so sorely due.</dialog>
                                    <node>
                                        <player>Wait… so you need me to wash your pants?</player>
                                        <dialog>In so many crude words, aye, that be my query.</dialog>
                                        <node ref="query" />
                                    </node>
                                    <node>
                                        <player>So that's what that smell was.</player>
                                        <dialog>Aye, a foul stench it be not even to comfort a beast, ne’er a man.</dialog>
                                        <node ref="query" />
                                    </node>
                                    <node>
                                        <player>Gross!</player>
                                        <dialog>As I spoke before.  Quite dire my friend.</dialog>
                                        <node ref="query" />
                                    </node>
                                    <node>
                                        <player>Um... ok.</player>
                                        <dialog>I thank you kind one.  I do verily thank thee.</dialog>
                                        <action quest="britches" />
                                    </node>
                                    <node id="special" cha="5">
                                        <player>Why don't you do it?</player>
                                        <dialog>Alas! What if I could? Think not of you would I?</dialog>
                                        <node>
                                            <player>Did that even make sense?</player>
                                            <dialog>Forsooth!</dialog>
                                            <node ref="special" />
                                        </node>
                                        <node>
                                            <player>Why can't you?</player>
                                            <dialog>With will there must also be means! I have much of the former and none of the later.</dialog>
                                            <node>
                                                <player>So if I gave you a bucket, soap and a brush you would do it yourself?</player>
                                                <dialog>...aye...</dialog>
                                                <action quest="britches" />
                                            </node>
                                        </node>
                                    </node>
                                </node>
                                <node>
                                    <player>Is this a joke?</player>
                                    <dialog>Good lord child no! This isn’t in the least a laughing matter.</dialog>
                                    <node ref="accepted" />
                                </node>
                            </node>
                        </node>
                        <node>
                            <player>Um... Yes?</player>
                            <dialog>STUPENDUS!  I like you with each passing second.  A remarkable being are you.  I feel my ease nestling in deeper in my very soul with each moment I converse with you.</dialog>
                            <node ref="accepted" />
                        </node>
                    </node>
                    <node>
                        <player>Uh, sure.  Why not?</player>
                        <dialog>Magnificent!</dialog>
                        <node ref="accepted"/>
                    </node>
                    <node>
                        <player>Um, what exactly am I accepting?</player>
                        <dialog>Is that doubt I hear? Oh no, can’t have any of that.  Only the surest of the sure.  Let’s try again.</dialog>
                        <node ref="ask" />
                    </node>
                </node>
                <exit>I should probably go.</exit>
			</conversation>
		</explination>
		<solved>
			<conversation person="mdav">
                <dialog></dialog>
                <node>
                    <person>How are those clean britches?</person>
                    <dialog>Words... cannot describe.</dialog>
                </node>
                <exit>Have a great day!</exit>
			</conversation>
		</solved>
	</quest>
</quests>